<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Guides on SLE BCI Documentation</title><link>/guides/</link><description>Recent content in Guides on SLE BCI Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to use container-suseconnect</title><link>/guides/container-suseconnect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/guides/container-suseconnect/</guid><description>What is container-suseconnect? container-suseconnect is a plugin available in all Base Container Images that ship with Zypper. When the plugin finds the host&amp;rsquo;s SUSE Linux Enterprise Server registration credentials, it uses them to give the container access the SUSE Linux Enterprise repositories. This includes additional modules and previous package versions that are not part of the free SLE_BCI repository.
How to use container-suseconnect If you are running a registered SLES system with Docker, container-suseconnect automatically detects and uses the subscription, without requiring any action on your part.</description></item><item><title>Using SLE BCI</title><link>/guides/using-sle-bci/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/guides/using-sle-bci/</guid><description>Package manager The default package manager in SUSE Linux Enterprise is Zypper. Similar to APT in Debian and APK in Alpine Linux, Zypper offers a command-line interface for all package management tasks. Below is brief overview of commonly used container-related Zypper commands.
Install packages zypper --non-interactive install $PACKAGE_NAME Add a repository zypper --non-interactive addrepo $REPOSITORY_URL; zypper --non-interactive refresh Update all packages zypper --non-interactive update Remove a package zypper --non-interactive remove --clean-deps $PACKAGE_NAME the --clean-deps flag ensures that no longer required dependencies are removed as well</description></item><item><title>Verify SUSE SLE Base Container Images With Cosign</title><link>/guides/verify-with-cosign/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/guides/verify-with-cosign/</guid><description>SUSE has SLE Base Container Images (BCI) that are great to use in workflows and as a based under your applications. One of the big reasons I like these images is that they are constantly updated with fixes for Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE). SUSE stays on top of this and takes security seriously.
For example, prior to writing this post I used Trivy to scan the Go image:
❯ trivy i registry.</description></item></channel></rss>