<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Documentations on SLE BCI Documentation</title><link>/documentation/</link><description>Recent content in Documentations on SLE BCI Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/documentation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BCI-Base, BCI-Minimal, BCI-Micro, and BCI-BusyBox</title><link>/documentation/general-purpose-bci/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/documentation/general-purpose-bci/</guid><description>SUSE offers several general-purpose SLE Base Container Images that are intended as deployment targets or as foundations for creating customized images: BCI-Base, BCI-Minimal, BCI-Micro, and BCI-BusyBox. These images share the common SLES base, and none of them ship with a specific language or an application stack. All images feature the RPM database (even if the specific image does not include the RPM package manager) that can be used to verify the provenance of every file in the image.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>/documentation/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/documentation/faq/</guid><description> What is SLE BCI?</description></item><item><title>Introduction to SLE Base Container Images</title><link>/documentation/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/documentation/introduction/</guid><description>SLE Base Container Image (SLE BCI) are minimal SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-based images that you can use to develop, deploy, and share applications. There are two types of SLE BCI:
General-purpose SLE BCI can be used for building custom container images and for deploying applications. Language stack SLE BCI provide minimal environments for developing and deploying applications in specific programming languages. In addition to that, we will provide Application Container Images based on SLE BCI featuring popular containerized applications like Nginx, PostgreSQL, MariaDB and RMT.</description></item><item><title>Language stack SLE Base Container Images</title><link>/documentation/language-stack-bci/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/documentation/language-stack-bci/</guid><description>If you have a working knowledge of containers, you will not have any difficulties using SLE BCIs. However, there are certain features that set SLE BCIs apart from similar offerings, like images based on Debian or Alpine Linux. And understanding the specifics can help you to get the most out of SLE BCIs in the shortest time possible.
Language stack SLE BCIs Language stack SLE BCI are built on top of BCI-Base.</description></item><item><title>Why SLE Base Container Images</title><link>/documentation/why-sle-bci/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/documentation/why-sle-bci/</guid><description>SLE BCIs offer a platform for creating SLE-based custom container images and containerized applications that can be distributed freely. SLE BCIs feature the same predictable enterprise lifecycle as SLES. The SLE_BCI 15 SP3 and SP4 repository (which is a subset of the SLE repository) gives SLE BCIs access to 4,000 packages available for the AMD64/Intel 64, AArch64, ppc64le, and s390x architectures. The packages in the repository have undergone quality assurance and security audits by SUSE.</description></item></channel></rss>